<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mas on Halixia</title>
    <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mas on Halixia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.halixia.com/ma/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1p saving challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/1p-saving-challenge-240/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/1p-saving-challenge-240/</guid>
      <description>Everyone can start an emergency fund
Here’s everything you need to know to make a start on saving for a rainy day, even if you are on limited income.
According to research up to a third of adults have none or less than £1,000 in savings. Regular saving provides good financial resilience, making you more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access job skills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/access-job-skills-274/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/access-job-skills-274/</guid>
      <description>Find training, support and advice to gain new job skills
Unlock a better way ahead. Find training, support, and advice to gain the skills you need for the job you want.
Digital, numeracy and transferable skills, like communicating confidently or handling stressful situations, are some of the most sought-after by employers. Developing these skills can strengthen your CV and help you stand out from the crowd.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score UK Government Free n/a UK Government Free n/a OpenLearn Free 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access job skills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/access-job-skills-276/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/access-job-skills-276/</guid>
      <description>Find training, support and advice to gain new job skills
Unlock a better way ahead. Find training, support, and advice to gain the skills you need for the job you want.
Digital, numeracy and transferable skills, like communicating confidently or handling stressful situations, are some of the most sought-after by employers. Developing these skills can strengthen your CV and help you stand out from the crowd.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score UK Government Free n/a Virtual College Free/Paid 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ageing issues</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/ageing-issues-290/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/ageing-issues-290/</guid>
      <description>Keep up to date with Age UK news
Learn about the issues affecting the elderly with news and views on age and ageing.
Your news, your stories, your later life. Discover the latest news and views on age and ageing – from analysis of what&amp;rsquo;s hitting the headlines, to the big issues affecting older people. Staying relevant helps retain a key interest in the world and keep your mind active.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art of calligraphy</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/art-of-calligraphy-260/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/art-of-calligraphy-260/</guid>
      <description>Learn the art of beautiful writing
Calligraphy can be described as the ancient art of writing words aesthetically. It is considered to be an art form, as it requires a considerable amount of patience and skill to master.
Not only is Calligraphy considered an art form, which can enhance the meaning and beauty of words, it also has numerous benefits for the physical and mental well-being of the individual. Calligraphy is known to improve cognitive function as well as help in increasing patience and focus of mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bake some bread</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/bake-some-bread-264/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/bake-some-bread-264/</guid>
      <description>Making freshly baked homemade bread is special
Making fresh bread at home is a satisfying and rewarding skill. From mixing and proving to shaping and baking, making delicious homemade loaves isn&amp;rsquo;t easy to master without some help and guidance.
Homemade bread is more nutritious and tastier than the store-bought variety as you can control what goes in it. Aside from the nutritional value, baking your own bread is good for your mental health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be your own boss</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/be-your-own-boss-328/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/be-your-own-boss-328/</guid>
      <description>Guidance on becoming your own boss
Starting a business or becoming self-employed is a life-long dream for many and it can also be risky, so legal, and financial aspects need to be carefully considered.
As you get older finding meaningful work that works flexibly can be difficult, despite your experience and knowledge. Starting a business takes care of that obstacle. After a lifetime of work in your chosen career, it could be the perfect time to revisit your passions and turn them into a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become multi-lingual</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/become-multi-lingual-292/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/become-multi-lingual-292/</guid>
      <description>Find out which language matches your learning style
Discover what type of learner you are and which language you should learn. Certain languages might come more naturally to certain people.
Learning languages improves memory, increases attention span and strengthens both problem-solving abilities and concentration. Multilingual people have also been shown to be more logical, have stronger decision-making skills and be more perceptive and aware of their surroundings.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Rocket Language Paid 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of reading</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/benefits-of-reading-340/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/benefits-of-reading-340/</guid>
      <description>Why you should try and read every day
Listen to this podcast and explore how losing yourself in a novel for a short time each day can boost your brainpower, improve social bonds and, surprisingly, help you live longer.
We live in an age where we can spend hours bingeing on TV box sets or surfing social media. But despite these distractions, reading remains a popular pastime. The health benefits are great, as is the opportunity to be transported to another world without even leaving your sofa!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Zumba</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/benefits-of-zumba-159/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/benefits-of-zumba-159/</guid>
      <description>Learn about the benefits of Zumba
Find out more about this global dance inspired fitness activity. It’s a great way to dance to great music, with great people, and burn a ton of calories!
Zumba is a dance class that features high and low intensity intervals that help improve cardiovascular fitness while also enhancing balance, coordination, agility, and to some degree, strength through the application of beginner-accessible choreography.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Zumba Free 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bills-only account</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/bills-only-account-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/bills-only-account-200/</guid>
      <description>A simple and easy way to manage money well
Know all your monthly bills are covered, your yearly expenses are sorted and you know how much you have to spend each month with a separate bills only account.
It’s a simple way to manage your day-to-day expenses without worrying you&amp;rsquo;ll run out of money each month. In addition, you&amp;rsquo;ll soon see where you might be wasting money, giving you more money to spend on the things that are important to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book dinner out</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/book-dinner-out-350/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/book-dinner-out-350/</guid>
      <description>Try somewhere new for dinner with a friends or family
Open Table enables diners to find and book the perfect table for every occasion, creating opportunity for human connection—among diners and restaurants, and between restaurants and their communities.
By eating meals together we practice gratitude. While sharing and enjoying a tasty meal with those who are the closest to you, you feel happy and more content as well as help to foster a sense of security and belonging, and even alleviate depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boost tax efficiency</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-tax-efficiency-216/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-tax-efficiency-216/</guid>
      <description>Use these methods to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re not paying too much tax
One of the simplest methods to make your money go further is to reduce your tax burden. Making even little modifications to your tax situation will save you a lot of money.
It’s no secret that being smart with your money and adopting good money habits can have a positive impact on our everyday lives. Financial wellbeing put simply is all about building a good relationship with money and feeling in control of both your day-to-day finances and long-term goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boost your income</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-your-income-204/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-your-income-204/</guid>
      <description>Read about opportunities to earn a second income
Learn how to boost your income. There are many ways to earn extra money, whether selling stuff, working from home or using the web.
In the current climate more than one stream of income can help you spread your bets and ensure that we’re always covered financially. Financial security is just one of the benefits of having multiple income streams, it can help you reach your financial goals earlier and build long-term wealth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boost your pension</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-your-pension-227/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-your-pension-227/</guid>
      <description>How to boost retirement saving with contribution matching
Some employers will pay more into your pension if you agree to increase your contributions. It might help you build your retirement savings faster.
Your future self will thank you for investing time in your retirement savings today. Making regular affordable contributions to a pension will help you to have the retirement you want.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score MoneyHelper Free 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Borrow a doggy</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/borrow-a-doggy-378/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/borrow-a-doggy-378/</guid>
      <description>Connect with dog owners and borrow their dog for walks
BorrowMyDoggy connects people who don&amp;rsquo;t own a dog with dog owners to help look after their dog, for walks, weekend, and holidays.
Spending time with a dog can greatly improve your mood, thereby helping you to have a more positive perspective. This can help create healthier relationships, improved productivity, and a significant improvement in your overall well-being as well as reducing stress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain training</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/brain-training-173/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/brain-training-173/</guid>
      <description>Exercise you cognitive skills with this program
Discover what your mind can do with activities to help exercise your memory, processing speed and problem solving and more.
Brain training turns inactive brain cells into healthy, active ones. The more you use your brain, the better your mental functions become. So, get strengthening your brain daily to start improving your cognitive capabilities.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Lumosity Free 2.2 Braingymer Free N/A Elevate Free/paid N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carer wellbeing</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/carer-wellbeing-370/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/carer-wellbeing-370/</guid>
      <description>Learn about managing your wellbeing while caring for others
Help in understanding how to manage your own wellbeing when caring for someone else. Get information and tips on looking after your mental health and finding support.
Looking after yourself is a really important part of caring for someone else. It will help you to feel happier and healthier, which will help you to cope better with your caring responsibilities.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Mind Free 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cashflow planning</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/cashflow-planning-230/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/cashflow-planning-230/</guid>
      <description>Bring together all of your assets, income and expenditure
Look at how cashflow planning can build income sustainability in retirement and help inform a discussion about appropriate levels of investment risk.
It’s no secret that being smart with your money and adopting good money habits can have a positive impact on our everyday lives. Financial wellbeing put simply is all about building a good relationship with money and feeling in control of both your day-to-day finances and long-term goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centre of Excellence</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/centre-of-excellence-312/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/centre-of-excellence-312/</guid>
      <description>Learn a new skill with online platform Centre of Excellence
Centre of Excellence offers opportunity to learn a new skillset for life or possibly take the next step into using the techniques to set up a rewarding new business. Centre of Excellence offers courses in many &amp;lsquo;small business specialisms&amp;rsquo; and complementary therapies, opening up opportunity to start your own business and new career direction. The online Business Support Group can help you make your dream of opening an exciting new business a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chair based exercise</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/chair-based-exercise-147/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/chair-based-exercise-147/</guid>
      <description>Try a chair-based workout
Get stronger, improve your flexibility and fitness. Here’s some chair based exercises you can do at home to stay strong, steady and independent as we age so we can keep doing the things we enjoy.
As we age we tend to lose muscle and keeping our muscles strong is vital, to prevent falls and support independent living. Even a small amount of activity can be a boost to our mental and physical wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change in income?</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/change-in-income-236/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/change-in-income-236/</guid>
      <description>Impartial guide to how to deal with a reduction in income
If, for one reason or another, you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing a reduction in income Money Navigator can help you get back on track.
You can still build good money habits even if you&amp;rsquo;ve experienced a reduction in income. Good financial resilience makes you more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combat loneliness</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/combat-loneliness-400/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/combat-loneliness-400/</guid>
      <description>Think about volunteering your time to help combat loneliness
Learn more about volunteering in your area
Volunteering gives you that opportunity to ‘pay it forward’ or to give something back in a selfless way. Helping you to connect with others while being good for the mind and body.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Happiness Free N/A Scouts Free N/A Guide dogs Free N/A This post contains affiliate links. If you use these links to buy something we may earn a commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consider investing</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/consider-investing-228/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/consider-investing-228/</guid>
      <description>Investing can be a great way to get your money to grow
This simple checklist will help you decide whether you&amp;rsquo;re ready to start your investment journey, when to invest and whether you have a few things still to tick off before exploring your options.
Investing in stocks &amp;amp; shares is a popular alternative to cash. On average, stockmarkets consistently outperform most cash savings over longer periods (5+ years), but you can experience losses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Considering a degree</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/considering-a-degree-332/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/considering-a-degree-332/</guid>
      <description>Flexible distance learning with the Open University
As experts in distance learning The Open University provides world-leading teaching strategies, meaning you’ll get a great learning experience that works flexibly for you.
The Open University is expert in distance learning and online courses its helped over 2 million people fulfil their potential and open up their future whatever their age. The OU’s unique, flexible approach to learning means you can fit study around your job, family, friends and leisure time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact old friends</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/contact-old-friends-346/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/contact-old-friends-346/</guid>
      <description>Re-connect with those people you may have lost touch with
Reconnect with an old friend, after you have kids, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to let friends slip away. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to get back in with your buddies.
Don’t wait to reconnect with the people who were once important to you. They will likely respond with gratitude and delight. Make the effort. It’s time to reconnect with a few old friends.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Fatherly Free 2 New York Times Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cook for the family</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/cook-for-the-family-366/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/cook-for-the-family-366/</guid>
      <description>Easy family friendly dinner ideas
Keep everyone happy with these easy family friendly dinner ideas. There&amp;rsquo;s pasta, of course, but also plenty of easy bakes and crunchy breaded goodies.
By eating meals together we practice gratitude. While sharing and enjoying a tasty meal with those who are the closest to you, you feel happy and more content as well as help to foster a sense of security and belonging, and even alleviate depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coursera courses</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/coursera-courses-308/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/coursera-courses-308/</guid>
      <description>Career advancing courses from Coursera
Online learning platform Coursea offers more than 5,000 courses, Professional Certificates, and degrees from world-class universities and companies. Start, switch, or advance your career.
Coursera is one of the most popular online learning platforms with a huge range of courses. It offers a range of payment options with 2,600+ free courses to kickstart your learning habit.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Coursera Free/paid 1.6 Upskillwise Free n/a Masterclass Paid 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dance</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/dance-151/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/dance-151/</guid>
      <description>Why dancing can enhance your fitness and mood
Learn about how you can two-step, boogie and bop your way to improved mood, muscle strength, and brain volume, and even a longer and healthier life.
Dance is a great way to stay in shape and can also help your heart. The aerobic effect of dance is great for overall fitness whilst the gentle impact of the turns and steps can help to protect against bone diseases, while also making you feel great too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes awareness</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/diabetes-awareness-128/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/diabetes-awareness-128/</guid>
      <description>All you need to know about diabetes
Diabetes is a lifelong condition that causes your blood sugar levels to become too high. There are two types of diabetes and you can reduce the risk of type 2 diabetes with simple lifestyle changes.
One in ten people over 40 in the UK are now living with type 2 diabetes, thats three.8 million people. Almost a million more are living with the condition but don&amp;rsquo;t know they have it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital buddy</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/digital-buddy-324/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/digital-buddy-324/</guid>
      <description>Could you be a digital buddy and help others get online
Do you know your way around a computer and feel confident in helping someone else? Find out about volunteering your time as a digital buddy, encouraging others to get online.
In an increasingly digital world it&amp;rsquo;s great when everyone benefits from technology. Growing someone else&amp;rsquo;s digital skills can help them be digitally able, equal and safe, so they can be happier, healthier and better off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover museums</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/discover-museums-288/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/discover-museums-288/</guid>
      <description>Discover museums to visit from all over UK
Discover museums to visit from all over UK, no matter what your interests are, with this independent museum listing site in the UK.
Museums and galleries provide an insight into the history of humankind. And while no museum can claim to provide a complete picture, the lessons we can learn from past events, wonders and tragedies are priceless. Stay curious!
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Museums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do a money makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/do-a-money-makeover-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/do-a-money-makeover-223/</guid>
      <description>How to refresh your finances and save over the year
This guide will help you understand how to overhaul your finances to save money by saving on bills and ensuring you&amp;rsquo;ve got the best deal on everything.
Building good money habits and making simple savings on everyday spending helps build good financial resilience. As result you will be more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eat mindfully</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eat-mindfully-181/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eat-mindfully-181/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to eat mindfully, for lasting change
Noom aims to empower you to take control of your health for good and meet personal health and wellness goals, including weight management, though delicious balanced healthy recipe boxes.
A healthy diet rich in fruits, vegetables, wholegrains and low-fat dairy can help to reduce your risk of heart disease by maintaining blood pressure and cholesterol levels as well as strengthening your immune system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eat well</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eat-well-171/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eat-well-171/</guid>
      <description>Information and guidance on eating a healthy balanced diet
A healthy, balanced diet is an important part of maintaining good health, making sure to eat the right amounts from a wide variety of food can help you achieve and maintain a healthy body weight.
A healthy diet rich in fruits, vegetables, wholegrains and low-fat dairy can help to reduce your risk of heart disease by maintaining blood pressure and cholesterol levels as well as strengthening your immune system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating together</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eating-together-344/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eating-together-344/</guid>
      <description>The benefits of eating together with friends and family
Eating meals together improves mood, combats feelings of isolation, and even improves self-image.
By eating meals together we practice gratitude. While sharing and enjoying a tasty meal with those who are the closest to you, you feel happy and more content as well as help to foster a sense of security and belonging, and even alleviate depression.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Am Dietics Free N/A BBC Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating together</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eating-together-368/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/eating-together-368/</guid>
      <description>Cook for your younger family members
There&amp;rsquo;s mountains of research about the social emotional and intellectual benefits of the family dinner, so cook a few extra spuds and invite the grandchildren round.
By eating meals together we practice gratitude. While sharing and enjoying a tasty meal with those who are the closest to you, you feel happy and more content as well as help to foster a sense of security and belonging, and even alleviate depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family history</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/family-history-360/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/family-history-360/</guid>
      <description>?Explore your family&amp;rsquo;s story with historical records
Using digitised historic records connect to people, both past and present, and visualise your family story in more detail than ever before.?
Knowing, recording, and preserving your family history directly impacts you, your family, by helping to develop a strong sense of who you really are. In discovering your family story, you create your own narratives about yourself helping to establish your unique, authentic core family identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family online safety</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/family-online-safety-270/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/family-online-safety-270/</guid>
      <description>Get practical knowhow keeping your family safe online
Young people are growing up in an increasingly digital world, exposing them to both the opportunities and risks of the internet. Get savvy on how you can protect yourself and your family when online.
Get practical advice on how to protect yourself, your computers and mobiles device and your business against fraud, identity theft, viruses and many other problems encountered online.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Get Safe Online Free n/a National Cyber Security Centre Free n/a National Cyber Security Centre Free n/a This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find a new activity</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/find-a-new-activity-161/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/find-a-new-activity-161/</guid>
      <description>Activity inspired by women doing their thing their way!
This Girl Can, celebrates active women and believes that there’s no “right” way to get active. However, you jiggle, kick, lift, stretch, or sprint, it’s time to get moving how you damn please!
It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to get active. No matter how much you do, physical activity is good for your body and mind. Adults should aim to be active every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find peer support</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/find-peer-support-376/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/find-peer-support-376/</guid>
      <description>Learn more about peer support to support your mental health
Learn more about peer support and how it can help you in a judgment-free, confidential space to be open about your mental health.
When facing a mental health crisis, it&amp;rsquo;s normal to feel alone or afraid to ask for help. That’s why having a good support network is incredibly important and has the potential to increase your confidence, mood and wellbeing and ultimately your health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire safety</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/fire-safety-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/fire-safety-126/</guid>
      <description>The importance of fire safety in the home
Read about the importance of fire safety in your home, to help keep you and your loved ones safe in the event of a fire and how to prevent them in the first place.
The best way to minimise the risk of fire is to take the threat seriously and put in place fire prevention measures. Understanding potential triggers, installing fire alarms, smoke alarms and other devices along with making and sharing fire safety plans are all ways to reduce the risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football for fitness</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/football-for-fitness-163/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/football-for-fitness-163/</guid>
      <description>Football based health programme to support a healthier you
Fit fans has helped football fans to achieve long-term improvements in weight loss, physical activity, diet and general wellbeing with fun football based activity programmes.
It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to get active. No matter how much you do, physical activity is good for your body and mind. Adults should aim to be active every day. Some is good, more is better still.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free language course</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/free-language-course-302/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/free-language-course-302/</guid>
      <description>Check out free language courses available
Whether it’s French, German, Spanish, Italian or Japanese you’d like to learn, there&amp;rsquo;s free language courses available for you.
Learning a language improves memory, increases attention span and strengthens both problem-solving abilities and concentration. Multilingual people have also been shown to be more logical, have stronger decision-making skills and be more perceptive and aware of their surroundings.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Alison Free/paid 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fund an emergency</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/fund-an-emergency-246/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/fund-an-emergency-246/</guid>
      <description>An emergency fund is a step towards financial security
Building an emergency fund can help prevent you needing to borrow money or make difficult financial decisions, by giving you savings to fall back on. How much you need, will depend on your situation.
According to research up to a third of adults had no or less than £1,000 in savings. Regular saving provides good financial resilience, making you more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FutureLearn</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/futurelearn-310/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/futurelearn-310/</guid>
      <description>Online learning with world class universities and experts
Futurelearn is a UK based learning platform, partnering with world-leading academic institutions known for their teaching and research across a variety of fields.
FutureLearn&amp;rsquo;s ExpertTracks will help you master new skills in a specialist job area with a focus on highly marketable skills. Subscribe to a series of in-depth courses and build practical expertise to earn a digital certificate and showcase your new skills to employers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Games with friends</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/games-with-friends-342/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/games-with-friends-342/</guid>
      <description>Online drawing &amp;amp; guessing game to play with friends &amp;amp; family
Have fun with friends and family even if not together by playing online games to stay connected.
Is there anything more enjoyable than playing games with friends? Not only is it a fun way to socialise, but research shows that it also has numerous health benefits. From improving cognitive function to reducing stress levels, playing games with friends can help you stay healthy and happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get active</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-active-139/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-active-139/</guid>
      <description>Help to get you moving and stay moving, whatever your age
However you&amp;rsquo;re feeling right now, and whatever you&amp;rsquo;re dealing with, getting and staying moving more will help you feel better for longer.
Regular physical activity or exercise helps your brain, heart and lungs stay healthy, and keeps your body strong and flexible.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Age UK Free N/A NHS Free 1.5 The Body Coach Free 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get active</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-active-167/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-active-167/</guid>
      <description>Physical activity is good for your body and mind
It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to get active. No matter how much you do, physical activity is good for your body and mind. Try these tools, tips and special offers to move more every day.
Regular physical activity or exercise helps your brain, heart and lungs stay healthy, and keeps your body strong and flexible.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score NHS Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get digital skills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-digital-skills-272/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-digital-skills-272/</guid>
      <description>Get skills and confidence in accessing digital tech
Find a centre near you offering help to build skills and confidence in accessing digital technology.
In an increasingly digital world it&amp;rsquo;s great when everyone benefits from technology. Growing your digital skills can help you be digitally able, equal and safe, so you can be happier, healthier and better off.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Online Centre Network Free n/a Age UK Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get into running</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-running-149/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-running-149/</guid>
      <description>Couch to 5k, work up towards running 5km in just 9 weeks
Taking up running can seem like a scary prospect, but the NHS couch to 5K will help you gradually work up towards running 5km in just 9 weeks, through a guided mix of walking and running.
Running is a great way to improve your overall physical health. It can improve heart and lung health, increase joint strength and stability and improve your mental wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get into TED Talks</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-ted-talks-326/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-ted-talks-326/</guid>
      <description>Spark your curiosity with a TED talk
TED talks are short powerful talks of free knowledge from the world&amp;rsquo;s most inspired thinkers. Get inspired with this list of the most popular TED talks.
TED is on a mission to discover and spread ideas that spark imagination, it is devoted to curiosity, reason, wonder and the pursuit of knowledge. It helps people gain a deeper understanding of the world and connection with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get into yoga</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-yoga-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-yoga-143/</guid>
      <description>Read about the benefits of yoga for the over 50s
Read about how starting yoga later in life does require adjustments and the practice itself changes as we age, for the better! Yoga after 50 is a time for moving inward, and that’s a positive thing.
Yoga is for everyone, whatever ability or disability, age, experience, fitness or bendiness and you can do it anywhere and anytime. Finding a yoga practice that’s right for you is worth the effort as it helps deepen the neural grooves that help us enjoy the benefits that regular practice brings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get into yoga</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-yoga-145/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-yoga-145/</guid>
      <description>Learn about the benefits of adding yoga into your life
Read about the benfits of yoga for everyone. Getting into a regular practice offers so many mental and physical health benefits. Some, like improved flexibility, are clearly evident.
Yoga is for everyone, whatever ability or disability, age, experience, fitness or bendiness and you can do it anywhere and anytime. Finding a yoga practice that’s right for you is worth the effort as it helps deepen the neural grooves that help us enjoy the benefits that regular practice brings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get new skills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-new-skills-278/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-new-skills-278/</guid>
      <description>Innovative learning for a new career
Online learning platforms provide access to courses that span across industries from accounting all the way to tourism, to help you upskill and start a new career.
Online learning can be a be modern and innovative way to keep learning and help you retrain for a new career. As adults, it can be all too easy to forget that learning remains important but staying open to new experiences can help you into your dream career regardless of age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give blood</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/give-blood-382/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/give-blood-382/</guid>
      <description>Learn about giving blood
Most people can give blood if they are fit and healthy, but there are some rules for donor to follow, find out if you can be a blood donor.
Giving blood saves lives. The blood you give is a lifeline in an emergency as well as for people who need long-term treatments.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score NHS Blood &amp;amp; Transplant Free 1.5 Healthline Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy ageing habits</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/healthy-ageing-habits-114/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/healthy-ageing-habits-114/</guid>
      <description>Read about research backed healthy habits for a longer life
Learn more about research backed healthy daily habits to help you live a longer life.
Start improving your life by adding these small healthy ageing habits to improve your body and mind
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Everyday health Free N/A Vagaro Paid N/A Family wall Free N/A This post contains affiliate links. If you use these links to buy something we may earn a commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help local wildlife</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/help-local-wildlife-394/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/help-local-wildlife-394/</guid>
      <description>Find out how to get involved in helping local wildlife
If you have a love for nature, give back to your community by getting involved in helping wildlife, find out more about how you can help.
Daily contact with nature is linked to better health, reduced levels of chronic stress, reductions in obesity and improved concentration. Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Rspb Free 2.2 Barnacle hedgehogs Free N/A Wild life trust Free 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/holidays-120/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/holidays-120/</guid>
      <description>Importance of taking holidays
Holidays are not just for relaxation; they help us deal with stressors and contribute to our overall wellbeing. Can’t afford a holiday? You can also get the same effect with a day trip!
Taking holidays can be a great chance to escape your daily routine and see new places, whilst also improving your health or well-being.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Age UK Free N/A Leisure care Free N/A Tourism for all Paid N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holidays</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/holidays-122/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/holidays-122/</guid>
      <description>Importance of taking holidays
Holidays are not just for relaxation; they help us deal with stressors in life contribute to our overall wellbeing. Even setting aside holiday time and taking day trips can be beneficial.
Taking holidays can be a great chance to escape your daily routine and see new places, whilst also improving your health or well-being.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Thrive global Free N/A Bupa No 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be mind kind</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/how-to-be-mind-kind-124/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/how-to-be-mind-kind-124/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness and meditation tools for a healthier you
Mindfulness and meditation tools can help you create life-changing habits to support your mental health. Become your mind’s best friend, helping you get through tough times and find joy in every day.
It can be easy to rush through life without stopping to notice much. Start paying more attention to the present moment, to your own thoughts and feelings, and to the world around you, to improve your mental wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stay active</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/how-to-stay-active-165/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/how-to-stay-active-165/</guid>
      <description>Get support to be active with a long-term health condition
Help and support to be active with a long-term health condition. Understanding that everybody is unique and knowing when to be more active is just as important as accepting when you can’t.
Starting to become more active can be daunting, especially if you are managing a health condition. However, everyone can be active, no matter their age or physical condition. It’s completely free, and something we all have the power to start doing more of at any point in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immersive language</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/immersive-language-306/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/immersive-language-306/</guid>
      <description>Combine learning a new language with cultural experience
Learn a new language with in country courses to not only explore the language but the culture too. Taught by qualified native speaking teachers.
Learning a language improves memory, increases attention span and strengthens both problem-solving abilities and concentration. Multilingual people have also been shown to be more logical, have stronger decision-making skills and be more perceptive and aware of their surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join a gym</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-gym-157/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-gym-157/</guid>
      <description>Find a quality affordable gym where everybody is welcome
Pure Gym is friendly, supportive, and judgement-free space where you can come in, work out and leave feeling good. No matter your goals, there’s something for everyone.
People who belong to a gym not only exercised more, they also have better cardiovascular health outcomes. These health benefits were even greater for people who had a gym membership for more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join a library</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-library-318/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-library-318/</guid>
      <description>Find and join your local library, for many free services
Your local library provides many services such as book loans, CD rental and internet access. Some may offer reading events and 24-hour online services.
A public library is the biggest treasure known to local communities. It&amp;rsquo;s always free to join and what you find there might surprise you and do more than inspire just a love of reading.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score UK Government Free n/a Your Story Free n/a Nalitabali Free n/a This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join a shed</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-shed-374/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-shed-374/</guid>
      <description>Learn more about men&amp;rsquo;s peer support groups across the UK
Learn more about peer support and how it can provide a social connection whilst pursing shared practical interests.
When facing a difficult time in your life, it&amp;rsquo;s normal to feel alone and struggle to ask for help. That’s why having a good support network is incredibly important and has the potential to increase your confidence, mood and wellbeing and ultimately your health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join a social group</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-social-group-386/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-social-group-386/</guid>
      <description>Learn about the importance of joining social groups
Joining a social group is a great way to meet new people, learn new things, find support, get out of your comfort zone and pursue your passions.
We are social beings, and interacting with people is in our nature. But it also brings us benefits on a mental and physical level, social motivation and social contact can help to improve memory formation and recall and protects the brain from neurodegenerative diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Nextdoor</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-nextdoor-392/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-nextdoor-392/</guid>
      <description>Social network with people in your local area
Learn more about nextdoor, the social network for your local area. It&amp;rsquo;s where you can share news, events and even sell your unwanted stuff.
Social media can pave a good way for networking with people far and wide. You can connect with anyone you want on these platforms and build contacts for your personal and professional life.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Nextdoor Free 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join social media</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-social-media-358/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-social-media-358/</guid>
      <description>Join social media and reconnect with old friends
Social networking websites are a great way to keep in touch with family and friends, follow public figures and organisations, and meet people with similar interests or hobbies.
Social media can pave a good way for networking with people far and wide. You can connect with anyone you want on these platforms and build contacts for your personal and professional life.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Age UK Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the WI</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-the-wi-388/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-the-wi-388/</guid>
      <description>Learn about the importance of joining social groups
Joining a social group, such as the WI, is a great way to meet new people, learn new things, find support, get out of your comfort zone and pursue your passions.
We are social beings, and interacting with people is in our nature. But it also brings us benefits on a mental and physical level, social motivation and social contact can help to improve memory formation and recall and protects the brain from neurodegenerative diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Later life care cost</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/later-life-care-cost-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/later-life-care-cost-219/</guid>
      <description>Read about how income and assets can affect fees funding
When it comes to paying for care in later life, there’s no one size that fits all. How much it costs will depend on various factors, including your levels of wealth &amp;amp; income.
Many families are unprepared for a loved one needing to go into care and are often at crisis point before considering the financial impact. The inevitable anxiety and stress can be eased with more careful advance financial planning and research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn a language</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-a-language-298/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-a-language-298/</guid>
      <description>Learn a new language with videos from native speakers
Learn a new language and be able to watch lessons from native speakers to fully understand and absorb the language.
Learning a language improves memory, increases attention span and strengthens both problem-solving abilities and concentration. Multilingual people have also been shown to be more logical, have stronger decision-making skills and be more perceptive and aware of their surroundings.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Memrise Free 3 Fluent u Paid 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn a language</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-a-language-304/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-a-language-304/</guid>
      <description>Open up your world with a short languages course
Discover a new language, explore different cultures or learn more about the power of communication. It could lead to a more formal qualification or a new career.
With increasing demand for language skills in education, and more broadly across the economy in client-facing roles, the ability to communicate in more than one language could be your ticket to a new career, or your passport to a new life abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about memory</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-about-memory-118/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-about-memory-118/</guid>
      <description>Understanding and improving your memory
This podcast explains the different types of memory and how to improve your learning and memory abilities.
Brain training turns inactive brain cells into healthy, active ones. The more you use your brain, the better your mental functions become. So get strengthening your brain daily to start improving your cognitive capabilities.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score hubermanlab Free N/A Brain gymmer Free N/A A Cognitive connection Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about U3A</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-about-u3a-402/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-about-u3a-402/</guid>
      <description>A member run community to enjoy shared interests
Learn about u3a, a UK wide cooperative movement of people no longer in full time work to continue their educational, social, and creative interests in a friendly and informal environment.
We are social beings, and interacting with people is in our nature. But it also brings us benefits on a mental and physical level, social motivation and social contact can help to improve memory formation and recall and protects the brain from neurodegenerative diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to sculpt</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-how-to-sculpt-256/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-how-to-sculpt-256/</guid>
      <description>Have fun and get creative with pottery
You can create sculpture! Even if you’re just a beginner, you won’t believe what you can do! By understanding the basics, you will be surprised with what you can achieve in a short space of time.
So get creative and use sculpture as a way to take your mind off the world&amp;rsquo;s problems and learn a new creative skill. Creating with clay is a great natural high and something we can all try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn something new</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-something-new-316/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-something-new-316/</guid>
      <description>Live classes for older adults
Learn something new with live classes for older adults by older adults from anything from art to travel.
GetSetUp is an online community of people who want to learn new skills, connect with others and unlock new life experiences. GetSetUp believes people over 55 can do anything when they have the tools to discover, learn and connect.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score get set up Free/paid n/a Centre of excellence Paid 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learning-platforms-280/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/learning-platforms-280/</guid>
      <description>Help in choosing a suitable online learning platform
Help in choosing from the many online learning platforms available to ensure you get the best out of any learning experience.
Online learning can be a modern and innovative way to keep learning. As adults, it can be all too easy to forget that learning remains important. Staying open to new experiences, actively seeking out ways to learn and develop helps retain a keen interest in the world and your own self improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life insurance</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/life-insurance-238/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/life-insurance-238/</guid>
      <description>Get life insurance to provide for your dependants
If anyone depends on your income, planning for their future if the worst were to happen could be invaluable. Life insurance can be one of the cheapest ways to protect your family&amp;rsquo;s finances. Life insurance makes a huge difference to bereaved families. The loss of a partner will inevitably impact the family’s finances and their level of financial comfort. A life insurance payout can help them manage financially, with the mortgage, bills, childcare, or maintain a standard of living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong learning</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/lifelong-learning-286/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/lifelong-learning-286/</guid>
      <description>Age UK can help you find out about learning opportunities
Education is a great way to learn something new, meet people, acquire new skills or have an active retirement. Advice from Age UK can help you make the most of learning opportunities available.
As adults, it can be all too easy to forget that learning remains important. Staying open to new experiences, actively seeking out ways to learn and develop helps retain a keen interest in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of all development MAs</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/content-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/content-list/</guid>
      <description>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-nap-100
https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-tips-102
https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-trackers-guide-104
https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-break-106
https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-meditation-108
https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-care-110
https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-care-112
https://www.halixia.com/ma/healthy-ageing-habits-114
https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-affirmations-116
https://www.halixia.com/ma/learn-about-memory-118
https://www.halixia.com/ma/holidays-120
https://www.halixia.com/ma/holidays-122
https://www.halixia.com/ma/how-to-be-mind-kind-124
https://www.halixia.com/ma/fire-safety-126
https://www.halixia.com/ma/diabetes-awareness-128
https://www.halixia.com/ma/the-nhs-healthcheck-130
https://www.halixia.com/ma/regular-health-check-131
https://www.halixia.com/ma/your-gut-microbiome-133
https://www.halixia.com/ma/mediterranean-diet-135
https://www.halixia.com/ma/start-exercising-137
https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-active-139
https://www.halixia.com/ma/stay-active-141
https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-yoga-143
https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-yoga-145
https://www.halixia.com/ma/chair-based-exercise-147
https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-into-running-149
https://www.halixia.com/ma/dance-151
https://www.halixia.com/ma/track-your-activity-153
https://www.halixia.com/ma/mobility-workout-155
https://www.halixia.com/ma/join-a-gym-157
https://www.halixia.com/ma/benefits-of-zumba-159
https://www.halixia.com/ma/find-a-new-activity-161
https://www.halixia.com/ma/football-for-fitness-163
https://www.halixia.com/ma/how-to-stay-active-165
https://www.halixia.com/ma/get-active-167
https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-better-169
https://www.halixia.com/ma/eat-well-171
https://www.halixia.com/ma/brain-training-173
https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-175
https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-177
https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-179
https://www.halixia.com/ma/eat-mindfully-181
https://www.halixia.com/ma/private-health-tests-183
https://www.halixia.com/ma/virtual-yoga-studio-184
https://www.halixia.com/ma/resistance-training-186
https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-188
https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-190
https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-192
https://www.halixia.com/ma/peak-brain-training-194
https://www.halixia.com/ma/use-micronutrients-196
https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-therapy-198
https://www.halixia.com/ma/bills-only-account-200
https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-money-202
https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-your-income-204
https://www.halixia.com/ma/use-spending-rules-206
https://www.halixia.com/ma/pay-off-debt-early-208
https://www.halixia.com/ma/maximise-savings-210
https://www.halixia.com/ma/pay-yourself-first-212
https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-your-savings-214
https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-tax-efficiency-216
https://www.halixia.com/ma/optimise-pensions-217
https://www.halixia.com/ma/later-life-care-cost-219
https://www.halixia.com/ma/need-a-money-plan-221
https://www.halixia.com/ma/do-a-money-makeover-223
https://www.halixia.com/ma/pensions-basics-225
https://www.halixia.com/ma/boost-your-pension-227
https://www.halixia.com/ma/consider-investing-228
https://www.halixia.com/ma/cashflow-planning-230
https://www.halixia.com/ma/track-your-portfolio-232
https://www.halixia.com/ma/need-an-advisor-234</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live class languages</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/live-class-languages-296/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/live-class-languages-296/</guid>
      <description>Learn a new language with live online classes
Learn a new language quickly and efficiently in a fun and interesting environment that also has the benefit of live classes to help get you speaking a new language.
Learning a language improves memory, increases attention span and strengthens both problem-solving abilities and concentration. Multilingual people have also been shown to be more logical, have stronger decision-making skills and be more perceptive and aware of their surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a will</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/make-a-will-252/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/make-a-will-252/</guid>
      <description>Wills are important whether or not you have very much
Most people who are married, have dependants or have any assets would likely benefit from making a will, to ensure your assets are passed on as you wish.
Research from insurer Canada Life in 2020 revealed three in five of UK adults have not written a will. This is equivalent to 31 million people, who run the risk of the law deciding who their assets are left to when they die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage bills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-bills-244/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-bills-244/</guid>
      <description>Minimise and manage bills for extra peace of mind
Guide to how to manage your bills closely to avoid penalities and start cutting out anything that is not a necessity.
Building good money habits and making simple savings on everyday spending helps build good financial resilience. As result you will be more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage money</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-money-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-money-202/</guid>
      <description>Start at the beginning and get to grips with managing money
Taking the time to manage your money better can really pay off. Learning to budget can help you stay on top of your bills and save.
It’s a simple way to manage your day-to-day expenses without worrying you&amp;rsquo;ll run out of money each month. In addition, you&amp;rsquo;ll soon see where you might be wasting money, giving you more money to spend on the things that are important to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage your savings</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-your-savings-214/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/manage-your-savings-214/</guid>
      <description>Savings platforms may help you achieve better rates
You could manage all your savings in one place through a savings platform. As well as convenience you could access consistently competitive rates from multiple banks and building societies.
Savings platforms offer you the opportunity to manage your savings all in one place. Great of you regularly switch accounts to get better rates as you&amp;rsquo;ll only need to register once to access a range of products from financial institutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximise savings</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/maximise-savings-210/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/maximise-savings-210/</guid>
      <description>Learn about the tax efficient savings accounts
Make sure you don’t pay more tax than you need to, with this guide to tax-free savings and investments for you and your children or grandchildren.
Since 2016, the personal savings allowance sets an amount of savings interest you can earn without paying tax on that interest. The amount of the allowance depends on much tax you pay, £1,000 in savings interest a year, for a basic rate taxpayer, and £500, for a higher rate taxpayer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediterranean diet</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/mediterranean-diet-135/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/mediterranean-diet-135/</guid>
      <description>Understand the health benefits of a Mediterranean diet
Traditionally, the Mediterranean diet is based on fruits, vegetables, seafood, nuts, dairy, olive oil, and maybe a glass of red wine. It is linked to lower disease outbreak and longer lifespans.
Rich in flavourful ingredients like fruits, vegetables, wholegrains, and heart-healthy fats, the Med diet is equal parts delicious and nutritious. It’s also associated with a variety of benefits and may help support brain function, promote heart health, regulate blood sugar levels, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobility workout</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/mobility-workout-155/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/mobility-workout-155/</guid>
      <description>Try mobility exercises to help increase flexibility
Read more about how a specific mobility workout will help improve your flexibility.
Mobility training optimizes movement and performance by increasing the range of motion within your joints and surrounding muscles. The benefits of mobility training are wide-ranging, helping with everything from pain and muscle soreness to form and strength.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Health Free 3.8 The Lean Machines Free N/A Builtlean Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money &amp; ill health</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/money--ill-health-248/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/money--ill-health-248/</guid>
      <description>Guide to managing money during periods of ill health
If you’re facing a health problem, try and sort out your money situation as soon as you can. This guide covers benefits entitlement, local council support, and where to get help with everyday costs.
You can still build good money habits even if you&amp;rsquo;ve experienced a reduction in income. Good financial resilience makes you more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murder mystery night</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/murder-mystery-night-348/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/murder-mystery-night-348/</guid>
      <description>How to host a murder mystery night
Read top tips on how to set up the perfect murder mystery dinner party for friends and family.
Is there anything more enjoyable than playing games with friends? Not only is it a fun way to socialise, but research shows that it also has numerous health benefits. From improving cognitive function to reducing stress levels, playing games with friends can help you stay healthy and happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need a money plan?</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/need-a-money-plan-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/need-a-money-plan-221/</guid>
      <description>Take control of your finances with smart financial goals
Make tangible differences in your financial life to redress the money gender gap. Spring clean your finances and you will enhance your financial and personal wellbeing.
In 2022 the gender pay gap reached 8.3% in 2022, meaning women in the UK take home less income compared to their male counterparts. The impact of this gender pay gap has led to a savings gap too, money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need an advisor?</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/need-an-advisor-234/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/need-an-advisor-234/</guid>
      <description>How do you know when it’s time to find an advisor?
If you’re looking to invest, buy a financial product, manage your money more effectively or simply plan for the longer term, getting a financial advisor can be a good investment.
Feeling in control of both your day-to-day finances and long-term goals can have a positive impact on our everyday lives. Maximising your financial wellbeing through investments can completely change your mindset and this will have a big impact on your behaviours and long-term financial goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neighbourly chat</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/neighbourly-chat-354/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/neighbourly-chat-354/</guid>
      <description>Help look out for your elderly neighbours
Volunteer your time and energy to help older people live a happy, connected, and purposeful later life.
Over one million older people say they go more than a month without speaking to a friend, neighbour or family member. But small acts of kindness can create a big difference.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Careline Free 4.6 National care line Free N/A Community access network Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neighbourly chat</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/neighbourly-chat-356/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/neighbourly-chat-356/</guid>
      <description>Make a difference by checking in on your neighbours
Check out our five simple tips for making a new connection in under five minutes, whether that’s with someone familiar or someone new and unexpected. You never know the difference it could make.
Over one million older people say they go more than a month without speaking to a friend, neighbour or family member. But small acts of kindness can create a big difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New business ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/new-business-ideas-330/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/new-business-ideas-330/</guid>
      <description>Ideas for starting your own business in retirement
Starting a new business in retirement doesn’t need to be a huge endeavour. It&amp;rsquo;s not about working like crazy just having something enjoyable to give a sense of fulfilment and satisfaction.
As you get older finding meaningful work that works flexibly can be difficult, despite your experience and knowledge. Starting a business takes care of that obstacle. After a lifetime of work in your chosen career, it could be the perfect time to revisit your passions and turn them into a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New creative skills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/new-creative-skills-258/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/new-creative-skills-258/</guid>
      <description>Explore Skillshare&amp;rsquo;s range of creative skills courses
Not sure what creative art to try, Skillshare has a range of creative courses from popular to very niche skills. Explore new skills, deepen existing passions, and get lost in creativity.
It doesn’t matter how old we are research suggests that having a creative hobby can actually benefit our mental and emotional health. The arts can help to keep us well, aid recovery and support people to live longer and healthier lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New social activity</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/new-social-activity-384/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/new-social-activity-384/</guid>
      <description>Find social activities near you
Find social activities offered at your local Age UK with activities such as bridge, photography club, pub lunch and tea dance and so much more.
We are social beings, and interacting with people is in our nature. But it also brings us benefits on a mental and physical level, social motivation and social contact can help to improve memory formation and recall and protects the brain from neurodegenerative diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutritional support</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-175/</guid>
      <description>How nutrition and lifestyle factors can affect your health
Read about nutrition and lifestyle factors and how these can affect women&amp;rsquo;s health, to support anyone on their journey towards a healthy, sustainable diet.
Good nutrition is getting the right amount of nutrients in the right combinations to help boost and strengthen our immune system, leading to healthier, more energetic, longer life.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score British Nutrition Foundation Free N/A BBC Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutritional support</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-177/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-177/</guid>
      <description>How nutrition and lifestyle factors can affect your health
Read about nutrition and lifestyle factors and how these can affect men&amp;rsquo;s health, to support anyone on their journey towards a healthy, sustainable diet.
Good nutrition is getting the right amount of nutrients in the right combinations to help boost and strengthen our immune system, leading to healthier, more energetic, longer life.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score British Nutrition Foundation Free N/A Lloyds pharmacy Free 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutritional support</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-179/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-support-179/</guid>
      <description>How nutrition and lifestyle factors can affect your health
Read about the nutrition and lifestyle factors that may play a role in ensuring older adults can lead not only longer but healthier lives.
Good nutrition is getting the right amount of nutrients in the right combinations to help boost and strengthen out immune system, leading to healthier, more energetic, longer life.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score British Nutrition Foundation Free N/A Active health Free N/A Nutritional meal plans Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutritional therapy</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-therapy-198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/nutritional-therapy-198/</guid>
      <description>Support for a healthier relationship with food
Nutritional therapy is the practice of using food, supplements and healthy diets, tailored towards helping you reach your health goals through a healthy relationship with food.
Good nutrition is getting the right amount of nutrients in the right combinations to help boost and strengthen our immune system, leading to healthier, more energetic, longer life.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Nutritionist-Resource Free/Paid 3.6 Nutrition Free N/A Active health Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimise pensions</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/optimise-pensions-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/optimise-pensions-217/</guid>
      <description>Learn about combining your pensions for ease and efficiency
Understand the advantages, and possible disadvantages, of bringing all your pensions together.
A key part of retirement planning is understanding what you’ve got and what you need in later life. The average person in the UK changes job every five years, and that means trying to keep track of several different pension plans. Putting it all in one pot can help simplify things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pay off debt early</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/pay-off-debt-early-208/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/pay-off-debt-early-208/</guid>
      <description>Help in tackling debts head on
If you&amp;rsquo;re juggling several different debts the best thing you could do is to tackle them head-on and get on track to becoming debt-free. But where do you start?
Debt can cause financial strain whereby high repayments can affect your ability to budget and you end up paying back much more than you borrowed. Also, when debt becomes unmanageable it is closely related to poor physical and mental health and affect current and future financial wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pay yourself first</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/pay-yourself-first-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/pay-yourself-first-212/</guid>
      <description>How to set aside money for savings before you pay expenses
Saving some money each month is important, even if it’s just a little. There is a psychological boost to seeing your savings or investments grow.
According to research up to a third of adults have none or less than £1,000 in savings. Regular saving provides good financial resilience, making you more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak brain training</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/peak-brain-training-194/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/peak-brain-training-194/</guid>
      <description>An app for complete brain training.
Challenge your cognitive skills, focus, memory, problem solving, mental agility and more, with these games designed to push you hard with short, intense workouts to fit around your life.
Brain training turns inactive brain cells into healthy, active ones. The more you use your brain, the better your mental functions become. So, get strengthening your brain daily to start improving your cognitive capabilities.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Peak Free N/A Mindamate Free N/A Protectstudy Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer support</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/peer-support-372/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/peer-support-372/</guid>
      <description>Learn more about men&amp;rsquo;s peer support groups across the UK
Learn more about peer support and how it can help you in a judgment-free, confidential space to be open about the storms in your life.
When facing a mental health issue, it&amp;rsquo;s normal to feel alone or afraid to ask for help. That’s why having a good support network is incredibly important and has the potential to increase your confidence, mood and wellbeing and ultimately your health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pensions basics</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/pensions-basics-225/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/pensions-basics-225/</guid>
      <description>Understand your pensions and what you may need in retirement
How much do you need in retirement and how much are you going to have?
Your future self will thank you for investing time in your retirement savings today. Making regular affordable contributions to a pension will help you to have the retirement you want.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score MoneyHelper Free 2.7 MoneySavingExpert.com Free 2.1 MoneyHelper Free 2.7 This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan an allotment</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/plan-an-allotment-362/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/plan-an-allotment-362/</guid>
      <description>Guide on how to choose what to grow in your allotment
It makes sense to try and grow what you like to eat and what lifestyle choices, but this needs to be looked at in terms of what is possible to grow. Learn more about choosing what to grow.
Did you know that gardening can also play an important role in happiness and mental well-being? The health benefits of gardening are many, from reducing stress and depression to even boosting your immune system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan your legacy</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/plan-your-legacy-255/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/plan-your-legacy-255/</guid>
      <description>Use an advisor who specialises in later life planning
The Society of Later Life Advisors is a not for profit organisation that matches clients with advisors who have been accredited to give advice on later life issues.
Financial wellbeing put simply is all about building a good relationship with money and feeling in control of both your day-to-day finances and long-term goals. This is also true when planning how you are going to pass your money to your loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private health care?</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/private-health-care-250/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/private-health-care-250/</guid>
      <description>How taking out private medical insurance works
Private healthcare is paid-for medical treatment. It&amp;rsquo;s an alternative to free treatment on the NHS. It can be costly, but taking out private medical insurance to pay for it can help.
Private medical insurance is designed to cover you for non-routine tests and treatment for acute conditions; typically those that are serious, curable and usually short-lived. It gives peace of mind that you can get treatment quickly and be back on your feet sooner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private health tests</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/private-health-tests-183/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/private-health-tests-183/</guid>
      <description>Guide to choosing the best private health check for you
Help in choosing the right private health test, with so much choice and so many different aspects to focus on, it can be hard to know if you are choosing the right private health check for you.
Health checks often focus on preventative health, helping to detect problems in their early stages and risk factors for certain conditions that might run in your family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional wills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/professional-wills-254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/professional-wills-254/</guid>
      <description>Find a specialist legal professional for your will
Using a legal professional who specialises in writing wills and other estate matters could be crucial especially if you have more complex affairs.
Financial wellbeing put simply is all about building a good relationship with money and feeling in control of both your day-to-day finances and long-term goals. This is also true when planning how you are going to pass your money to your loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainy day savings</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/rainy-day-savings-242/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/rainy-day-savings-242/</guid>
      <description>Everyone can start an emergency fund
An emergency fund is easy to start and can save you from an unexpected crisis. Here’s everything you need to know to start saving for a rainy day.
According to research up to a third of adults have none or less than £1,000 in savings. Regular saving provides good financial resilience, making you more likely to cope with loss of income, less anxious about finances, more confident in managing money and more satisfied with life as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read to learn</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/read-to-learn-300/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/read-to-learn-300/</guid>
      <description>Learn a new language by reading
Learn a new language by reading and listening to the narrations, to help you become more comfortable with the words and grammatical rules of your chosen language.
Learning a language improves memory, increases attention span and strengthens both problem-solving abilities and concentration. Multilingual people have also been shown to be more logical, have stronger decision-making skills and be more perceptive and aware of their surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular health check</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/regular-health-check-131/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/regular-health-check-131/</guid>
      <description>Learn more about why you should get a health check
Even if exercise, eat right and feel healthy, its useful to get a regular health check to understand if there are any undelying risks to your future health.
The best way to maintain health is to preserve it. Regular health checks not only help identify underlying medical conditions, but they can also guide you to options that speed up the recovery process and help you maintain and/or improve your overall health and wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resistance training</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/resistance-training-186/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/resistance-training-186/</guid>
      <description>Change the way you exercise in later life
Instepp is designed to activate, tone, and strengthen your whole body using established methods of exercise that combine the benefits of resistance training with fundamental movement.
Resistance training improves muscle strength and tone and protects your joints from injury. It also is a relatively accessible option that can help you reach your weight management goals as well as maintain flexibility and balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-affirmations</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-affirmations-116/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-affirmations-116/</guid>
      <description>Benefits of using self-affirmations
There are many benefits of using self-affirmations including reducing health deteriorating stress and anxiety. Learn about the benefits of using self-affirmations in your life .
Start working on improving your stress, anxiety, and self-worth with the use of self-affirmations to get all the benefits that come with it.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Happier human Free N/A refined by age Free N/A Get help Free 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-care</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-care-110/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-care-110/</guid>
      <description>The importance of self-care
With busy modern lives we often tend to put ourselves last however, self-care is crucial in maintaining functional health. Read more about why it&amp;rsquo;s important to get some time to take care of yourself.
Start engaging in self-care, to help you to relieve the pressures of everyday life and reset yourself to get back to a healthy point where productivity is once again maximised.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score The couples centre Free N/A Simple lion heart life Free N/A me time therapy Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-care</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-care-112/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/self-care-112/</guid>
      <description>The importance of self-care
With busy modern lives we often tend to put ourselves last however, self-care is crucial in maintaining functional health. Read more about why it&amp;rsquo;s important to get some time to take care of yourself.
Start engaging in self-care, to help you to relieve the pressures of everyday life and reset yourself to get back to a healthy point where productivity is once again maximised.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score The couples centre Free N/A Simple lion heart life Free N/A me time therapy Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share an interest</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/share-an-interest-390/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/share-an-interest-390/</guid>
      <description>Creating a shared interest group
Learn more about starting your own shared interest group.
We are social beings, and interacting with people is in our nature. But it also brings us benefits on a mental and physical level, social motivation and social contact can help to improve memory formation and recall and protects the brain from neurodegenerative diseases.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Meet up Free 1.5 Q place Free N/A Wiki how Free 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Better</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-better-169/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-better-169/</guid>
      <description>Tips on how to get a better night&amp;rsquo;s sleep
Learn everything you need to know about sleep, including how to fall asleep faster, stay asleep and wake up rested as well as how it can improve your health.
Sleep is an essential function to help our mind and body recharge. Healthy sleep also helps the body remain healthy and stave off diseases. Without enough sleep, the brain cannot function properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep tips</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-tips-102/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-tips-102/</guid>
      <description>Find out how to increase the quality of your sleep
One of the most common problems related to ageing is sleep quality, with over half of older adults reporting symptoms of insomnia. Read tips on how to better increase your sleep quality.
Sleep is an essential function to help our mind and body recharge. Healthy sleep also helps the body remain healthy and stave off diseases. Without enough sleep, the brain cannot function properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep trackers guide</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-trackers-guide-104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/sleep-trackers-guide-104/</guid>
      <description>Guide to sleep trackers
Read a guide to the best sleep trackers to help you make an informed decision when buying one for yourself, to help you get a good night of restful sleep.
Tracking your sleep can help you to better understand your sleep habits, helping you to learn what is potentially helping or harming your sleep.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score The dozy owl Free N/A Consensus sleep diary Free N/A Sleep on Paid N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a shed</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/start-a-shed-398/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/start-a-shed-398/</guid>
      <description>How to set up a Men&amp;rsquo;s Shed as a safe place for men to meet
Men’s Sheds are a place to pursue practical interests, to practice skills and enjoy making and mending - whilst making social connections and friendship - set one up and help men in your community.
We are social beings, and interacting with people is in our nature. But it also brings us benefits on a mental and physical level, social motivation and social contact can help to improve memory formation and recall and protects the brain from neurodegenerative diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start exercising</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/start-exercising-137/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/start-exercising-137/</guid>
      <description>A simple workout series to help begin your fitness journey
Start your exercise journey with easy-to-follow exercise sessions designed for beginners.
Regular exercise is one of the best things you can do for your health. However, working it into your routine and sticking with it can take some determination and discipline, but if you exercise regularly, you’ll begin to see and feel the benefits it can have on your body and well-being quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay active</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/stay-active-141/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/stay-active-141/</guid>
      <description>Help to keep you moving, whatever your age
However you&amp;rsquo;re feeling right now, and whatever you&amp;rsquo;re dealing with, this site can help you get moving more so you&amp;rsquo;ll feel better for longer.
Regular physical activity or exercise helps your brain, heart and lungs stay healthy, and keeps your body strong and flexible.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Psych reg Free N/A Livestrong Free 3.2 Stay Fit Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay safe online</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/stay-safe-online-268/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/stay-safe-online-268/</guid>
      <description>Get practical know how on staying safe online
Practical advice on how to protect yourself, your computers and mobiles device and your business against fraud, identity theft, viruses and many other problems encountered online.
Cyber security is important because smartphones, computers and the internet are now such a fundamental part of modern life, that it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to imagine how we&amp;rsquo;d function without them.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Get Safe Online Free n/a National Cyber Security Centre Free n/a Action Fraud Free n/a This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying in ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/staying-in-ideas-364/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/staying-in-ideas-364/</guid>
      <description>Fun ideas for a great night in
Post-pandemic, we are all bit more used to staying in, why not try one of these ideas to mix it up a bit.
Is there anything more enjoyable than playing games with friends? Not only is it a fun way to socialise, but research shows that it also has numerous health benefits. From improving cognitive function to reducing stress levels, playing games with friends can help you stay healthy and happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support the arts</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/support-the-arts-352/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/support-the-arts-352/</guid>
      <description>8 ways you can support your local arts community
Find out how to support your local arts community and know you are helping build a healthy, robust and diverse society.
When you think of some of the most culturally diverse and renowned cities on Earth, they all have one thing in common a healthy vibrant arts scene. From local galleries to life-size wall murals, a community full of art is a community full of culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tailored supplements</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-188/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-188/</guid>
      <description>Find out how to meet your nutritional requirements
Healthspan offers supplements for women of all ages, from PMS support, to conception, to the menopause.
Supplementation is intended to bridge this nutritional gap, so that we maintain the proper balance of nutrients from food and supplementation. This will enhance the nutrient density of your diet and make sure you are obtaining the right amount of nutrients tailored to your dietary needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tailored supplements</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-190/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-190/</guid>
      <description>Find out how to meet your nutritional requirements
Healthspan has a range of vitamins and supplements to support you as you get older to help maintain your health.
Supplementation is intended to bridge this nutritional gap, so that we maintain the proper balance of nutrients from food and supplementation. This will enhance the nutrient density of your diet and make sure you are obtaining the right amount of nutrients tailored to your dietary needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tailored supplements</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-192/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tailored-supplements-192/</guid>
      <description>Find out how to meet your nutritional requirements
Healthspan offers a wide variety of vitamins and supplements tailored specifically to men&amp;rsquo;s health and wellbeing.
Supplementation is intended to bridge this nutritional gap, so that we maintain the proper balance of nutrients from food and supplementation. This will enhance the nutrient density of your diet and make sure you are obtaining the right amount of nutrients tailored to your dietary needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a break</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-break-106/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-break-106/</guid>
      <description>Find out about the importance of taking a break
This episode of the &amp;ldquo;Just one Thing&amp;rdquo; podcast introduces the importance of taking a break to boost focus, enhance creativity and even improve your eye health.
Taking breaks can be beneficial to both you and what you are working on, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a micro break, lunch break or longer break, give yourself a break.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score BBC Free 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a nap</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-nap-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-nap-100/</guid>
      <description>Why an afternoon nap can be beneficial
Listen to a podcast explaining the joys of an afternoon nap. It’s not a lazy snooze, it’s a brain booster! Napping can help your heart, improve your mood, and enhance your memory.
Naps have been shown to have numerous benefits including improving cognitive functions such as memory, logical reasoning, and the ability to complete complex tasks. Naps have also been shown to help improve cardiovascular health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a writing class</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-writing-class-266/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-a-writing-class-266/</guid>
      <description>Discover a love for creative writing with a class
Take an online writing class to learn how to write, whether your interest is fiction, articles or non-fiction, find a writing workshop best suited for you and get writing.
To learn creative writing, like any art form, requires compassion, contemplation, and curiosity. There are benefits in making you a better communicator, improve your thinking skills, increase empathy and could even lead to greater job success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take up chess</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-up-chess-262/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/take-up-chess-262/</guid>
      <description>Start taking chess lessons to improve cognitive function
Chess is one of the oldest and most popular board games. The board represents a battlefield in which two armies fight to capture each other’s king. Chess is a game of skill and strategy.
Chess has been shown to have many benefits from stress reduction to improving cognitive function, start taking chess lessons to learn to play chess, or revive a lost skill, and enjoy the benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach creative arts</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/teach-creative-arts-334/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/teach-creative-arts-334/</guid>
      <description>Find out how you could teach creative arts on Skillshare
Skillshare allows you to create courses where you can teach others your creative skills. Get acquainted with its approach to teaching online and everything you need to get started.
If you’re an experienced creative pro with tips, techniques and skills to demonstrate you could help others along their creative journey, it’s rewarding in more ways than one. By teaching on Skillshare, you can grow your online following, give back, and earn money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach with Udemy</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/teach-with-udemy-336/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/teach-with-udemy-336/</guid>
      <description>Find out how to become an Udemy instructor and change lives
Udemy offers free course creation with easy-to-follow steps to help in the creation of your course, which will consist of videos and lectures with the option to add assignments and quizzes.
Teach what you know and help learners explore their interests, gain new skills, and advance their careers. It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding in more ways than one, you get to share your passion, as well as continue to develop your knowledge and understanding of that passion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The NHS healthcheck</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/the-nhs-healthcheck-130/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/the-nhs-healthcheck-130/</guid>
      <description>A health check-up for adults 40 to 74 in England
This check-up is for adults in England aged 40 to 74, every 5 years. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to spot early signs of stroke, kidney disease, heart disease, type 2 diabetes or dementia.
After the check your healthcare professional will discuss your results with you. You&amp;rsquo;ll be given advice to help you lower your risk of a stroke, kidney disease, heart disease, diabetes or dementia, and maintain or improve your health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track your activity</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/track-your-activity-153/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/track-your-activity-153/</guid>
      <description>Track your walks or runs to see improvements in your health
You might already be walking or running regularly, a tracking app like MapMyWalk can you help you set goals and stay motivated. You can also use it to find new popular routes in your area.
Research has shown that consistently using a fitness tracker, can help motivate you to increase your phyisical activity by making you more accountable to yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track your portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/track-your-portfolio-232/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/track-your-portfolio-232/</guid>
      <description>How to understand and track your investment portfolio
Track your investments, get a clear picture of your assets and understand your portfolio performance.
Feeling in control of both your day-to-day finances and long-term goals can have a positive impact on our everyday lives. Maximising your financial wellbeing through investments can completely change your mindset and this will have a big impact on your behaviours and long-term financial goals.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Morningstar Free 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transferable skills</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/transferable-skills-322/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/transferable-skills-322/</guid>
      <description>The importance of transferable skills
You are already likely to possess many transferable skills employers value. Highlighting your transferable skills is especially important when changing jobs or industries.
Many job seekers aren’t able to capture their transferable skills adequately, communicate them well or even identify how their skills can apply across industries. If you are seeking a career change transferable skills can be the factor that most impacts your ability to find work in a new field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tread the boards</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tread-the-boards-380/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/tread-the-boards-380/</guid>
      <description>Learn more about taking part in amateur theatre
Information and listings for amateur theatrical groups, schools, societies, choirs, troupes and clubs in your local area.
Taking part in amateur theatre, is a fun way to meet new people, form connections and have fun while helping to build your confidence and communication and public speaking skills.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Noda Free N/A Amdram Free N/A NDFA Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try a podcast</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-a-podcast-314/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-a-podcast-314/</guid>
      <description>Try a podcast
Dip your toe into a pick of the best podcasts on Spotify, Apple Podcasts and more covering technology, culture, science, politics, and new ideas.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve not discovered them yet, podcasts are a great learning tool. You can listen anywhere and access a wide range of topics.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Wired Free 1.3 Buffer free 2.8 TED Talks Free N/A This post contains affiliate links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try learning</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-learning-282/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-learning-282/</guid>
      <description>Get free learning from The Open University
OpenLearn is the home of free learning from The Open University. A huge range of topics for you to discover with 60-second animated videos or 24-hour courses all for free.
Online learning can be a modern and innovative way to keep learning, but we might not be sure what we want to do. Kickstart lifelong learning by trying some free courses and open up to new experiences and your own self improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try meditation</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-meditation-108/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-meditation-108/</guid>
      <description>Guided meditations to boost health
Try guided meditations hosted by a psychotherapist. Walking you through calm discussions of body and mind, helping you deal with life’s stresses or to help you destress after a long day.
Apart from enhancing your happiness and improving your overall well-being, meditation also helps your memory stay sharp and your concentration remain steady. Start working meditation into your life to reap the benefits.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Tara brach Free N/A The heart of meditation Paid N/A Yoga journal Paid 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try teaching</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-teaching-338/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/try-teaching-338/</guid>
      <description>Find out about teaching in Further Education
If you have real-world industry experience, you already have what it takes to teach in further education, and you don’t always need teaching experience or an academic degree to get started.
Teach what you know and help learners explore their interests, gain new skills, and advance their careers. It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding in more ways than one, you get to share your passion, as well as continue to develop your knowledge and understanding of that passion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use micronutrients</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/use-micronutrients-196/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/use-micronutrients-196/</guid>
      <description>Micronutrients to help improve health and longevity
Listen to podcast, talking about the four major categories of micronutrients that improve immune system and longevity and much more. With actionable protocols for obtaining key micronutrients.
Micronutrients, often referred to as vitamins and minerals, are vital to healthy development, disease prevention, and wellbeing. They have a wide range of functions in the brain and body, from the workings of the nervous system to immune function and bone strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use spending rules</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/use-spending-rules-206/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/use-spending-rules-206/</guid>
      <description>The 50-30-20 rule is a way to help manage your spending
Find out how this simple rule to share out your income can help you create some great spending habits.
This simple budgeting method requires less tracking than many others as it only gives you three categories to think about. It&amp;rsquo;s also flexible as you can allocate monies within the categories as you need and provides budget for more of the things you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual yoga studio</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/virtual-yoga-studio-184/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/virtual-yoga-studio-184/</guid>
      <description>Yoga and meditation classes you can practice anywhere
This online yoga studio includes ready-made classes to practice anywhere, choose your level, duration and focus see if you can find the perfect class for you.
Yoga is for everyone, whatever ability or disability, age, experience, fitness or bendiness and you can do it anywhere and anytime. Finding a yoga practice that’s right for you is worth the effort as it helps deepen the neural grooves that help us enjoy the benefits that regular practice brings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which language app?</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/which-language-app-294/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/which-language-app-294/</guid>
      <description>Find the right language learning platform for you
Digital technology has opened up loads of new ways to learn a language, making it very practical and affordable. Work out which is best for you before diving in and learning a second language.
Today&amp;rsquo;s top language learning platforms use innovative technology and modern study tools to make your learning process easier and more productive. Making accessing the benefits of learning a language easier for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why use trusts</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/why-use-trusts-253/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/why-use-trusts-253/</guid>
      <description>How to write life insurance in trust
Avoid potential inheritance tax and long delays in pay-out through using a trust to hold your life insurance.
Life insurance helps bereaved families manage financially, with the mortgage, bills, childcare, or maintain a standard of living. Getting that money quickly can make all the difference.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Which? Free/paid 1.6 This post contains affiliate links. If you use these links to buy something we may earn a commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplace support</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/workplace-support-320/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/workplace-support-320/</guid>
      <description>Help and support to think differently about working longer
Think differently about working as you get older. Staying in work and taking control of when and how you retire can give you more money in later life as well as benefit your health and wellbeing.
Get ahead and kep working the way you want. Employers in the UK waste a huge amount of talent, skills and experience by denying older workers the chance to stay in jobs or find new ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplace support</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/workplace-support-396/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/workplace-support-396/</guid>
      <description>Working women&amp;rsquo;s peer to peer support groups
Learn more about Leanin, where working women come together to learn from each other and achieve their goals, because women together can be a powerful force for change in the world.
Provider Free or Paid Trustpilot Score Leanin Free N/A NWR Free N/A Together friends Free N/A This post contains affiliate links. If you use these links to buy something we may earn a commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplace training</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/workplace-training-284/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/workplace-training-284/</guid>
      <description>Expand your employment opportunities
At Virtual College, there are courses to help you expand your employment opportunities. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s learning a new skill or complying with current legislation, this training platform can help.
Online learning can be a be modern and innovative way to keep learning and help you retrain for a new career. As adults, it can be all too easy to forget that learning remains important but staying open to new experiences can help you stay relevant in your chosen career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your gut microbiome</title>
      <link>https://www.halixia.com/ma/your-gut-microbiome-133/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.halixia.com/ma/your-gut-microbiome-133/</guid>
      <description>Learn about the impact of your gut microbiome on your health
Listen to this podcast episode to learn more about gut microbiome and enhancing to improve your brain and overall health.
Your gut microbiome is a vast community of trillions of bacteria and fungi that inhabit every nook and cranny of your gastrointestinal tract, and have a major influence on your metabolism, body weight, propensity to illness, immune system, appetite and mood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
